

GRAVILI ANDREA

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

ABOUT ME

I have been immersed in the field of Computer Science since a young age, harboring a keen interest in astronomy and consistently striving for excellence. This journey has honed my skills as a proficient problem-solver with a resolute commitment to advancing technological research.

EDUCATION

CONTACTS

- +39 375 604 5429
- andrea.gravili8egmail.com
- (BS) Italy, Vestone
- andreagravili.vercel.app
- in www.linkedin.com/in/andreagravili-b1b808254
- github.com/TitanWasHere

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Software engineering
- ROS programming
- Web programming
- Ul design

LINGUISTIC SKILLS

- Italian (mother tongue)
- English C1

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO

09/2021 - 07/2024

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

ITIS G.PERLASCA

09/2016 - 06/2021

High School degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

ROBOTICS SOFTWARE ENGINEER | 08/2024 - CURRENT University of Trento

Skills: ROS, C++, Python, software for the interaction with an humanoid robot, path planning, problem solving.

ROBOTICS SW. ENGINEER INTERN | 02/2024 - 06/2024 University of Trento

Skills: ROS, C++, Python, software for the interaction with an humanoid robot, path planning, problem solving

Goals achieved:

- Robot interaction with people at the Trento Museum of sciences "MUSE"
- Tested software in 2 big scenarios (University and MUSE)

UNIVERSITY TUTOR | 09/2023 - 02/2024 University of Trento

University tutor for the course: software engineering Skills: JS (node.js), react.js, HTML + CSS, building of a software architecture, Mongo DB, agile, leadership, communication, creativity

Goals achieved:

- Helped multiple students with their projects with positive feedback
- Better communication and teaching skills

O ICT TECHNICIAN | 06/2023 - 06/2024 University of Trento

Skills: Python, Ubuntu, computer architecture, teamwork, communication, Adaptability

DIGITAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES AND SIMIL

- C
- C++
- Python
- Java
- HTML+CSS
- Node.js
- MatLAB

- Vue.js
- React.js
- ROS
- PHP
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- R

COMPUTER BASICS

- Docker
- Git
- ____
- Unix
- Office

PROJECTS

ARI THESIS

02/2024 - 07/2024

Project for the University of Trento, which deals with a humanoid robot named ARI. My responsibility in this project is to manage the speech and listening node, as well as the calibration and path planning.

Github: github.com/TitanWasHere/ARI-thesis

TECH-DOWSER

02/2023 - 07/2023

The project for the university course 'Human-Computer Interaction', is a prototype of a potability water detector with a connected application that contains its position and data of the detected water.

Drive: https://drive.google.com/drive/u/0/folders/1YsaFhWc3lekWEJWNR3tJBMYu7FnEPleK

ISS4U

09/2022 - 09/2023

Project for the university course 'Software Engineering', it's an application to manage tasks on the International Space Station (ISS) and display data about that. The website is made with node.js

Github: https://github.com/SE-T28

HONOURS AND AWARDS

WINNER OF THE 2024 VENETOSTARS EDITION 22/05/2024

Won the 2024 VenetoStars project for developing a solution using space data to protect the UNESCO site of the Prosecco Hills. The project, named Safe-Hills, was presented at the Space Meeting 2024 in Venice.

Website: https://venetostars.com/#winnerd

D R I V I N G L I C E N S E

B